{"data":{"postgres":{"establishment":[{"establishmentid":"5359","name":"Detroit Shipping Company- Bars","address":"474 Peterboro St","zipcode":"48201","owner":"Jonathan Hartzell DSY Investme","licenseNumber":"229172","licenseType":"Fixed Establishment","establishmentType":"Food Service Establishment","establishmentStatus":"Open","riskCategory":"Medium","reviewFrequencyDays":"365.0","coords":"-83.06167,42.34422","geojson":{"id":"5359","type":"Feature","geometry":{"type":"Point","coordinates":[-83.0616724239999,42.3442225970001]},"properties":{"name":"Detroit Shipping Company- Bars","owner":"Jonathan Hartzell DSY Investme","address":"474 Peterboro St","zipcode":"48201","license_type":"Fixed Establishment","risk_category":"Medium","license_number":"229172","establishmentid":"5359","establishment_type":"Food Service Establishment","establishment_status":"Open","review_frequency_days":"365.0","most_recent_license_date":"5/22/2018"}},"nearbyList":[{"establishmentid":"51622714","name":"-320 Coffee & Creamery","address":"474 Peterboro Street #201","zipcode":"48201"},{"establishmentid":"51622705","name":"Brujo","address":"474 Peterboro St #105","zipcode":"48201"},{"establishmentid":"51622644","name":"Coop","address":"474 Peterboro St #104","zipcode":"48201"},{"establishmentid":"51622643","name":"Bangkok 96","address":"474 Peterboro Street #103","zipcode":"48201"},{"establishmentid":"5094","name":"Peterboro","address":"420 Peterboro ","zipcode":"48201"}],"inspectionsByEstablishmentidList":[{"inspectionid":"43486","inspectionDate":"2018-09-19T00:00:00","inspectionType":"Routine Inspection","inCompliance":"Yes","violationsByInspectionidList":[{"violationCode":"3-501.18","violationDescription":"A FOOD specified in ¶ 3-501.17(A) or (B) shall be discarded if it:  \r\n    (1) Exceeds the temperature and time combination specified in ¶ 3-501.17(A),              except time that the product is frozen; (P)\r\n    (2) Is in a container or PACKAGE that does not bear a date or day; (P) or\r\n    (3) Is appropriately marked with a date or day that exceeds a temperature and              time combination as specified in ¶ 3-501.17(A). (P)  \r\n\r\n","violationType":"Priority","itemDescription":"Ready to eat, potentially hazardous food(s)","subItem":"","problemDescription":"Beyond consume by date","subProblem":"","location":"WALK-IN COOLER","subLocation":"","corrected":"Yes","daysToCorrect":"10.0","correctedDate":"2018-09-19T00:00:00","correctionDescription":"Discard."},{"violationCode":"7-102.11","violationDescription":"Working containers used for storing POISONOUS OR TOXIC MATERIALS such as cleaners and SANITIZERS taken from bulk supplies shall be clearly and individually identified with the common name of the material. (Pf)\r\n","violationType":"Foundation","itemDescription":"Working containers-toxics","subItem":"","problemDescription":"Not labeled as to content","subProblem":"","location":"BAR","subLocation":"","corrected":"Yes","daysToCorrect":"10.0","correctedDate":"2018-10-05T00:00:00","correctionDescription":"Label containers with common name."},{"violationCode":"5-205.11","violationDescription":"(A) A HANDWASHING SINK shall be maintained so that it is accessible at all times for EMPLOYEE use and used for no other purpose. (Pf)\r\n(B)  An automatic handwashing facility shall be used in accordance with manufacturer's instructions. (Pf)\r\n","violationType":"Foundation","itemDescription":"Handwashing sink(s)","subItem":"","problemDescription":"Not easily accessible","subProblem":"Items stored In front of","location":"HANDSINK(S)","subLocation":"","corrected":"Yes","daysToCorrect":"10.0","correctedDate":"2018-09-19T00:00:00","correctionDescription":"Remove items from handsink.  Do not store items at handsink."},{"violationCode":"4-903.11","violationDescription":"Cleaned EQUIPMENT and UTENSILS, laundered LINENS, and SINGLE-SERVICE and SINGLE-USE ARTICLES shall be stored in an approved manner and location.\r\n","violationType":"Core","itemDescription":"Single-service/single-use article(s)","subItem":"","problemDescription":"Stored on floor or less than 6 inches above floor","subProblem":"","location":"DRY STORAGE AREA","subLocation":"","corrected":"Not required","daysToCorrect":"30.0","correctedDate":null,"correctionDescription":"Store at least 6 inches above the floor."},{"violationCode":"6-303.11","violationDescription":"Light of the proper intensity shall be provided as specified.\r\n","violationType":"Core","itemDescription":"Lighting intensity","subItem":"","problemDescription":"Not maintained","subProblem":"","location":"DRY STORAGE AREA","subLocation":"","corrected":"Not required","daysToCorrect":"30.0","correctedDate":null,"correctionDescription":"Maintain in good repair"}]},{"inspectionid":"43029","inspectionDate":"2018-07-10T00:00:00","inspectionType":"Preopening/New","inCompliance":"Yes","violationsByInspectionidList":[{"violationCode":"5-205.11","violationDescription":"(A) A HANDWASHING SINK shall be maintained so that it is accessible at all times for EMPLOYEE use and used for no other purpose. (Pf)\r\n(B)  An automatic handwashing facility shall be used in accordance with manufacturer's instructions. (Pf)\r\n","violationType":"Foundation","itemDescription":"Handwashing sink(s)","subItem":"","problemDescription":"Not used according to manufacturer's label instructions","subProblem":"","location":"BAR","subLocation":"","corrected":"Yes","daysToCorrect":"10.0","correctedDate":"2018-07-10T00:00:00","correctionDescription":"Use according to manufacturer label directions."},{"violationCode":"6-202.16","violationDescription":"Perimeter walls and roofs of a FOOD ESTABLISHMENT shall effectively protect the establishment from the weather and the entry of insects, rodents, and other animals.\r\n","violationType":"Core","itemDescription":null,"subItem":"","problemDescription":null,"subProblem":"","location":"WALK-IN COOLER","subLocation":"","corrected":"Not required","daysToCorrect":"30.0","correctedDate":null,"correctionDescription":null},{"violationCode":"4-101.19","violationDescription":"NonFOOD-CONTACT SURFACES of EQUIPMENT that are exposed to splash, spillage, or other FOOD soiling or that require frequent cleaning shall be constructed of a CORROSION-RESISTANT, nonabsorbent, and SMOOTH material.\r\n","violationType":"Core","itemDescription":null,"subItem":"","problemDescription":null,"subProblem":"","location":"BAR","subLocation":"","corrected":"Yes","daysToCorrect":"30.0","correctedDate":"2018-07-13T00:00:00","correctionDescription":null},{"violationCode":"4-402.11","violationDescription":"EQUIPMENT that is fixed because it is not EASILY MOVABLE shall be installed so that it is spaced to allow access for cleaning along the sides, behind, and above the EQUIPMENT or sealed as required,  COUNTER-MOUNTED EQUIPMENT that is not EASILY MOVABLE shall be installed to allow cleaning of the EQUIPMENT and areas underneath and around the EQUIPMENT .\r\n","violationType":"Core","itemDescription":"Fixed equipment","subItem":"","problemDescription":"Not sealed to adjoining","subProblem":"Equipment","location":"BAR","subLocation":"","corrected":"Yes","daysToCorrect":"30.0","correctedDate":"2018-07-13T00:00:00","correctionDescription":"Seal to wall/equipment to facilitate cleaning."},{"violationCode":"6-101.11","violationDescription":"Materials for indoor floor, wall, and ceiling surfaces under conditions of normal use shall be:\r\n(1) SMOOTH, durable, and EASILY CLEANABLE for areas where FOOD ESTABLISHMENT operations are conducted;\r\n(2) Closely woven and EASILY CLEANABLE carpet for carpeted areas; and\r\n(3) Nonabsorbent for areas subject to moisture such as FOOD preparation areas, walk-in refrigerators, WAREWASHING areas, toilet rooms, mobile FOOD ESTABLISHMENT SERVICING AREAS, and areas subject to flushing or spray cleaning methods.\r\n","violationType":"Core","itemDescription":"Wall material(s)","subItem":"for construction","problemDescription":"Not smooth and easily cleanable","subProblem":"","location":"BAR","subLocation":"WOOD","corrected":"Yes","daysToCorrect":"30.0","correctedDate":"2018-07-13T00:00:00","correctionDescription":"Repair/replace to be smooth."},{"violationCode":"6-303.11","violationDescription":"Light of the proper intensity shall be provided as specified.\r\n","violationType":"Core","itemDescription":"Lighting intensity","subItem":"","problemDescription":"Less than","subProblem":"10 foot candles","location":"BAR","subLocation":"Light intensity","corrected":"Yes","daysToCorrect":"30.0","correctedDate":"2018-07-13T00:00:00","correctionDescription":"Provide as required"},{"violationCode":"6-201.11","violationDescription":"Except otherwise approved, and except for antislip floor coverings or applications may be used for safety reasons, floors, floor coverings, walls, wall coverings, and ceilings shall be designed, constructed, and installed so they are SMOOTH and EASILY CLEANABLE.\r\n","violationType":"Core","itemDescription":"wall(s)","subItem":"","problemDescription":"Not constructed, designed, installed to be","subProblem":"","location":"WAREWASHING AREA","subLocation":"","corrected":"Yes","daysToCorrect":"30.0","correctedDate":"2018-07-13T00:00:00","correctionDescription":"Repair/replace to be smooth and easily cleanable."},{"violationCode":"6-304.11","violationDescription":"If necessary to keep rooms free of excessive heat, steam, condensation, vapors, obnoxious odors, smoke, and fumes, mechanical ventilation of sufficient capacity shall be provided.\r\n","violationType":"Core","itemDescription":"Mechanical ventilation","subItem":"","problemDescription":"Not provided","subProblem":"","location":"WAREWASHING AREA","subLocation":"","corrected":"Not required","daysToCorrect":"30.0","correctedDate":null,"correctionDescription":"Install to meet requirements"},{"violationCode":"4-402.11","violationDescription":"EQUIPMENT that is fixed because it is not EASILY MOVABLE shall be installed so that it is spaced to allow access for cleaning along the sides, behind, and above the EQUIPMENT or sealed as required,  COUNTER-MOUNTED EQUIPMENT that is not EASILY MOVABLE shall be installed to allow cleaning of the EQUIPMENT and areas underneath and around the EQUIPMENT .\r\n","violationType":"Core","itemDescription":"Fixed equipment","subItem":"","problemDescription":"Not sealed to adjoining","subProblem":"Equipment","location":"BAR","subLocation":"","corrected":"Yes","daysToCorrect":"30.0","correctedDate":"2018-07-13T00:00:00","correctionDescription":"Seal to wall/equipment to facilitate cleaning."},{"violationCode":"6-501.11","violationDescription":"PHYSICAL FACILITIES shall be maintained in good repair.\r\n","violationType":"Core","itemDescription":"Physical facilities","subItem":"","problemDescription":"In poor repair","subProblem":"","location":"WAREWASHING AREA","subLocation":"","corrected":"Yes","daysToCorrect":"30.0","correctedDate":"2018-07-13T00:00:00","correctionDescription":"Repair"}]}]}]}},"pageContext":{"eid":"5359"}}